# Elias Johnson

### Computer Science Undergraduate

+(541) 974-2350 | eliascarljohnson@gmail.com | linkedin.com/in/eliasjohnson- | https://elias-johnson.github.io/

#### PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

I am a passionate and diligent individual driven by the desire to serve others, a lifelong learner and problem solver with a sharp eye for the meticulous. I am proficient in multiple programming languages and paradigms such as object-oriented design and procedural/functional programming. Well-versed in version control and Agile methodologies, I have experience with the product development process, delivering quality work with a diverse team.

#### **EDUCATION**

#### **GEORGE FOX UNIVERSITY**

Newberg, OR

Bachelor of Science in Computer Science and Cybersecurity

August 2022 - Present

Minor in Music GPA: 3.89

#### **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

ProgrammingPython, Java, JavaScript, C++, Scala, ShellDevelopmentAgile Methodologies, Git, UML, Unit Testing

Web-Development HTML, CSS
Database SQL, PostgreSQL

**Networking** Subnetting, Routing Algorithms, Topology Design

Cybersecurity Autopsy, Burp Suite, Wireshark
Operating Systems Windows, Linux (Ubuntu, Debian)

#### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

BON APPÉTIT Newberg, OR

Associate, Part-Time

August 2022 - December 2024

At Bon Appétit, I work a variety of roles including ensuring the cleanliness of the dish room and kitchen, preparing food and drink at the café, and running the till and stocking shelves for the student store.

Skills: Organization, Time Management, Customer Service

## ALBANY PARTY STORE Albany, OR

Associate, Seasonal June 2018 - August 2024

At The Albany Party Store, I worked as one of the primary delivery drivers for rental items. I would also spend much of my time in the showroom, assisting customers on the phone or in-person with their orders.

Skills: Communication, Critical Thinking, Customer Service